Guide to "Yale Reports" Audio Recordings and Transcripts
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audio Recordings, 1956-1976; Series I; The audiotapes are 5.5" and 7.5" reel-to-reel.
  - Yale Reports '75-'76, Master Tape 34, Kaye & Cosell, 1976 May 23; 1 (Box 236)
  - Yale Reports '76-'77, #3, Looking Back on Government Service, Undated; 1 (Box 237)
  - Comer's Interview w/SEF, Undated; 1 (Box 238)
  - Giamatti Interview (on use of English Language), Undated; 1 (Box 239)
  - "Sizwe Banzi Lives!", Mr J. Kani, Mr A. Brown, Mr W. Ntshona, Undated; 1 (Box 240)
  - "Life Would Be Drab, Indeed, Without the Funnies", Mr W.K. Zinsser, Mr M.A. Walker, Undated; 1 (Box 241)
  - About John Sloan, American Artist, Undated; 1 (Box 243)
  - "Conversation avec M. Robbe-Grillet" (French), Kurt Forster, Alain Robbe-Grillet, Jacques Ehrmann, Undated; 1 (Box 244)
  - "The Professor as a Novelist", Mr Norman Holmes Pearson, Mr Robert Penn Warren, Undated; 1 (Box 245)
- Transcripts, 1955-1970, 1975; Series II
  - Volumes 1-3 [1-149], 1955-1959 (Box 246, Folder 1-3)
  - Volumes 4-5 [150-249], 1959-1962 (Box 247, Folder 1-2)
  - Volumes 6-7 [250-349], 1962-1965 (Box 248, Folder 1-2)
  - Volume 8 [350-399] and unbound transcripts [400-449], 1965-1967 (Box 249, Folder 1-4)
  - Volumes 10-11 [450-524], 1967-1969 (Box 250, Folder 1-2)
  - Volume 12 [525-573] and Volume for 1975, 1969-1970, 1975 (Box 251, Folder 1-2)
- Press Releases, 1962-1966; Series III
  - Episodes 266-416, 1962 December 2-1966 December 11 (Box 252)
    General
    The file for episode 409 contains research items and correspondence related to the broadcast.